<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: report | Blogy]]></title>
  <link href="http:///blog/categories/report/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http:///"/>
  <updated>2014-12-29T19:58:37-05:00</updated>
  <id>http:///</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Aziz Alto]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Into The Asian Bermuda Triangle: AirAsia Flight QZ8501]]></title>
    <link href="http:///blog/2014/12/29/into-the-asian-bermuda-triangle-airasia-flight-qz8501/"/>
    <updated>2014-12-29T19:53:30-05:00</updated>
    <id>http:///blog/2014/12/29/into-the-asian-bermuda-triangle-airasia-flight-qz8501</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Early yesterday around noon in New York time [now: Mon Dec 29 18:58:39 EST 2014], the malaysian airlines flight QZ85501 has gone missing after about 42 minutes of its flight from Surabaya, in Indoensia, to Singapore.
Until this moment the ongoing search efforts have not been successful. Although, the Indonesian authorities reported that the airplane could be at the pot of the ocean. Other reports, said that an Australian navy airplane have spotted some unidentified objects somewhere in the south east of the Indian Ocean. However, all these reports came out of some speculations which have no solid ground; since no wreckage, no crash signs, and no evindence yet could solve the mystery of disappearance of the flight.</p>

<p>Just three minutes before the airplane’s signal disappear from the radars, the pilot had requested to change the flight altitude from 32,000 feet to 38,000 feet due to a severe storm. That was the last contact between the airplane and the Indonesian flight control as reported by Indonesian Officials. Although, his request was rejected, still no one knows what had happened after that.</p>

<h3 id="unpleasant-meomories">Unpleasant Meomories</h3>

<p>This incident brings back to memories the other tragic disappearance of flight MH370 less than ten months ago on March 8th, which has an unknown fate until today.</p>

<p>The interesting thing is that both airplanes are owned by Malaysian based airlines. The two incidents also happened roughly in the same geographical area which is South East Asia. What a coincidence!! Could it be another Bermuda triangle in that part of the world?</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
